{
    "subject": "Frances_Hughes_Glendening",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Parris_Glendening",
    "human_readable": "Frances Hughes Glendening is married to Parris Glendening.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9885352253913879,
            "question": "Is Parris Glendening married to Frances Hughes Glendening?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9875611662864685,
            "question": "Is there a marriage between Frances Hughes Glendening and Parris Glendening?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9749440550804138,
            "question": "To whom is Frances Hughes Glendening married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9741074442863464,
            "question": "Who is Frances Hughes Glendening married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.967022180557251,
            "question": "Name the spouse of Frances Hughes Glendening."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9257681965827942,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Frances Hughes Glendening and Parris Glendening?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.875307023525238,
            "question": "What is the name of Frances Hughes Glendening's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8147890567779541,
            "question": "Who is Parris Glendening?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7923554182052612,
            "question": "What is Frances Hughes Glendening's marital status?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7729128003120422,
            "question": "Who shares a spousal relationship with Frances Hughes Glendening?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Frances Hughes Glendening is married to Parris Glendening.",
            "html": "yago_12755_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Frances Hughes Glendening's marital status?",
            "html": "yago_12755_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Parris Glendening?",
            "html": "yago_12755_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Frances Hughes Glendening's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_12755_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12755_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12755_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12755_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12755_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12755_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12755_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12755_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12755_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12755_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12755_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the requested JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The text explicitly states that Frances Hughes Glendening was married to former Maryland Governor Parris Glendening, and that they divorced while he was still governor (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_12755/re-ranker-msmarco/37.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information that supports the statement that Frances Hughes Glendening was married to Parris Glendening. For instance, `37.txt` and `29.txt` mention their marriage, with details such as when it took place, the duration of their relationship, and even the recent events leading up to Parris Glendening's third marriage involving Jennifer Crawford."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}